awesomeclassicgames.com 2016-10-12

# Privacy Policy | AwesomeClassicGames

## Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy

Your privacy is very important to us. Accordingly, we have developed this policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate and disclose and make use of personal information. The following outlines our privacy policy.

1\. Before or at the time of collecting personal information, we will identify the purposes for which information is being collected.

2\. We will collect and use of personal information solely with the objective of fulfilling those purposes specified by us and for other compatible purposes, unless we obtain the consent of the individual concerned or as required by law.

3\. We will only retain personal information as long as necessary for the fulfillment of those purposes.

4\. We will collect personal information by lawful and fair means and, where appropriate, with the knowledge or consent of the individual concerned.

5\. Personal data should be relevant to the purposes for which it is to be used, and, to the extent necessary for those purposes, should be accurate, complete, and up-to-date.

6\. We will protect personal information by reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.

7\. We will make readily available to customers information about our policies and practices relating to the management of personal information.

We are committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principles in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained. If you have problem related privacy issues, please contact us through email at webmaster@AwesomeClassicGames.com. We are committed to resolving any issues in a timely manner.

If you have questions or concerns regarding our Privacy Policy, you can reach us at

webmaster@awesomeclassicgames.com

c/o: Awesome Classic Games  
3700 Mansell Road, Suite 220  
Atlanta, Georgia 30022  
(404) 586-4392

Conditions of Use

By using and accessing AwesomeClassicGames.com you are agreeing to the Online Privacy Policy set forth. As our business changes and grows, we may change the privacy policy. Any changes will be posted on our site. Please check back often for any updates.
